Let's do an exercise of matching information in
section 2 together.
First, we're going to read the requirement, all
the questions and options, and then underline the keywords.
In this exercise, we will have to identify
what 6 student volunteers do to help others.
We will need to choose from a list
of 7 different options.
In step 2, we can find the following
keywords in the question, what, each, volunteers, and
help.
All of the options are our keywords and
we need to predict how they can be
paraphrased in the recording.
Let's practice our paraphrasing skill for
the options
in this exercise.
Awesome job!
And next, you will listen and find the
answers to these 6 questions in the practice
section.
For matching information, you have to take notes
next to the options when listening.
And don't forget the last step, which is
checking your answers after listening.
See you soon!